# MELISSA WARD

## UX/UI AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

mmacward99@gmail.com

wardmelissa.com

## SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

CSS & HTML

Figma

Github

Graphic Design

CMS Management

## EDUCATION

Media, Arts, and Design

James Madison University 2018-2022

\_\_\_\_\_

## AWARDS

2022

Hashtag Sports Award Co-Nominee

#### PROFILE

A UX/UI and Graphic Designer from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Since May of 2022 I have worked as Web Seasonal Associate for the Philadelphia Eagles, where I worked with the incredible team of Eagles Entertainment. I am a creative, adaptable, and hard-working individual with a passion for design.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Web Associate**

Philadelphia Eagles

2022-2023

- Co-led design on specialty campaigns for the Eagles' App and Website
- Collaborated effectively with other departments and external clients on projects
- · Created copy for digital platforms with editorial staff
- Created graphics, partner website pages and app experiences
- Updated CMS weekly supporting marketing and corporate partnerships
- Designed website headers and graphics for a variety of digital marketing campaigns
- Created forms for Sweepstakes, Super Bowl, Suite Occupancy, and Internal Operations

## **Digital Intern**

MidAtlantic Employers' Association

2021-2022

- Collaborated with Managing Director to edit PowerPoint decks
- Revamped templates to provide a current design to over 20 different PowerPoint decks
- · Maintained strong communication throughout remote internship
- Received positive feedback from multiple member companies/clients generating repeat business

# **Assistant manager**

Jules Thin Crust

2015-2021

- Created and managed employee schedules supporting the business while accommodating individual requests and requirements
- · Ensured employees complied with company policies and procedures
- Manage all team members on shift, including cooks, food runners, servers, and hosts
- Provided excellent customer service and when necessary responded quickly and efficiently to customer complaints to resolve issues